carolinamls.com 2012-11-19

# Privacy Policy

At the Charlotte Regional Realtor® Association (CRRA) and Carolina Multiple Listing Services, Inc. (CMLS), we recognize that privacy is important. This policy applies to all products, services and Web sites offered by CRRA and CMLS, or their subsidiaries or affiliated companies.

 **Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case we might not be able to provide those services to you. 

**Information sharing**

We do not share you personal information. We do not sell or otherwise distribute your e-mail address.

 **Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage, processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and might be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

We take security very seriously and therefore take every precaution to secure our members' information so your payment and personal information is always safe. To secure your information, we have implemented several security measures to prevent loss, theft or misuse of any borrower data.

Our Web site utilizes industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to allow for the encryption of potentially sensitive information, such as your name and address and other critically sensitive information like your credit card number.

To benefit from this security and to use many of the features on this site, you will need to download a 128-bit enabled browser from Microsoft, Netscape or another software company.

In addition to using 128-bit encryption in the browser, all credit card numbers that are stored in our databases are also encrypted.

We will accept returns if you are not satisfied with the product or due to manufacturing defect. All returns must be within 30 days of purchase and with your receipt. All form sales are final. 

All donations are final.
